# ADITYA PANDEY

### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

E +919792775342

adityapandey232003@gmail.com

**Portfolio:** 

https://adityapandey9882.github.io/Portfolio

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aditya-devp/ GitHub:

https://github.com/adityapande9882

# **EXPERIENCE**

### Internship in Front-end Web Development

#### **Cod Soft**

9 India

iii 05/2024 - 06/2024 ♀ Greater Noida

 Completed a specialized internship in front-end web development with cod soft

### AI-ML Virtual Internship

#### **AWS**

# 05/2023 - 07/2023 ♀ GREATER NOIDA

- Participated in an AI/ML virtual internship, enhancing skills in machine learning techniques and practical applications.
- · Highlight your accomplishments, using numbers if possible.

## **EDUCATION**

## B-Tech (7.2 CGPA)

#### **Mangalmay Institute of Engineering and Technology**

#### Intermediate

#### **Mahatma Gandhi Inter College**

#### High School

#### **Little Scholar Academy**

### **PORJECTS**

### Portfolio Profile

Designed and developed a comprehensive portfolio website to highlight a variety of projects and technical skills

Tools: HTML5, CSS, VS Code

#### Razor pay-clone

iii 06/2024 - 07/2024 ♀ Greater Noida

Utilized Tailwind CSS to create a visually appealing and highly responsive user interface

· Tools: Tailwind CSS, VS Code.

#### Food-Ordering-App

Created an interactive Food Ordering App designed to simplify the online ordering process and enhance user engagement

· Tools: Tailwind, React, VS Code

## **SUMMARY**

FULL STACK DEVELOPER As an enthusiastic Full Stack Developer, I've expertly wielded HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Reacts, MongoDB, Express, and Nodesjs to build sleek, responsive web applications. My drive for innovation and excellence fuels my passion for creating cutting-edge solutions and tackling complex challenges.

# TRAINING / Certification

#### **Certified Full-Stack Developer**

IIT Kanpur Technology

# Data Analytics, IBM Skills Build and CSRBOX Academic

IBM Skills Build and CSRBOX Academic

## **LANGUAGES**

#### **ENGLISH**

Intermediate

#### **HINDI**

Native

# 00000

# <u>SKILLS</u>

HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT

TAILWIND CSS REACTJS MONGODB

EXPRESSJS GIT GITHUB POSTMAN

**JAVA** 

### ACHIEVEMENTS

- The NSS Program volunteer helped organize events and spearhead social course awareness efforts as part of a community service project.
- Participant, International Conference on Interpretation – Received a certificate.
- Al Odyssey Skills Challenge Certificate (Microsoft)